clarintontrading.com 2011-09-12

# CLARINTON Trading - Security Information

## The news

* * *

06.09.2011 

Alert Pay Integration!

Alert Pay Integration! Dear respectable users, we do really apologize for the inconvenience that can be caused by a delay, however from now on you can easily use Alert Pay as another payment option for investments

02.08.2011 

Our survey is completed

Our survey is completed. We are very grateful to those who took part in it, in the nearest future you will see the results and appropriate changes in our company's work.

22.07.2011 

The survey

Dear users! We decided to make a survey and find out your attitude toward Clarinton Trading. We highly appreciate your opinion. Please answer several questions:   
1\. Are you satisfied with our company's activity?  
2\. Have you ever had any technical problems on the site, if so, please describe them.  
3\. Are you satisfied with the customer care support?   
4\. Please list the payment systems that you like, and you want us to work with in the future.   
5\. You could send us your comments and suggestions on the e-mail.  

07.05.2011 

Technical work is finished

Technical work is finished, instant payments work as usual.

05.05.2011 

Technical works

On the server conducted the technical work. Instant payments temporarily disabled.

* * *

read all news

## Privacy Policy

At CLARINTON Trading. ("CLARINTON Trading ", "we", "us", "our"), your personal data is important for us, so we do as much as possible to protect it safety and keep it from the third party. We take care about the trust that you have to CLARINTON Trading in order to create safe and secure medium for personal financial information.

This policy shows up how do we protect your information. This policy covers only our customers and those who was our customer. We comprehend the value of your personal data information, and do as much as possible to keep it in secure. Does not matter if you are just a visitor on our site, or our customer, we do as much as we can to keep all your data in safe location, and do not allow access to your information to third party.

We collect you data only if we believe this going to be useful for us, in our business, in order to make better offer to you regarding our services. If you need, submit a request and we will tell you all the information we collected about you, we want you to know that we collect information only if we believe, this information would be useful for our business. We use data to protect and administer funds, records and accounts; to check up with regulations and laws; if we believe this information will help us to develop or design better service; and to understand your requirements, to make our services more customer-friendly.

We also take some measures to make your data safer. We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We usually check all kind of safeties, as physical, electronic and other to be sure nobody could access your information.

Our web site and engine on it, in automated manner collect some information, as IP address, your browser name and other information regarding your system. To be more precise the following information : date and time of visit, domain name, IP address, actions, URLs, visited information received and sent (bytes), cookies, reference domain and operating system. We use this data to make our services easy to use for the most people whom may be interesting to use it.

In order to store our customers' preference information used on visiting our website, as well as to make the access to the restricted pages easier during one online web session, CLARINTON Trading makes use of cookies. Session cookies serve to verify the authenticity of your login information. The cookies are also used to perform the evaluation and tracking of all the web pages you've accessed while visiting our site. With this scope we unite all the received data with the data information placed on the pages visited by other users in order to make the overall track of visitor traffic patterns that helps us make the organization of our site better and, for instance, to estimate the efficiency of both, our advertising and marketing campaigns. Please note, that these cookies do not store any information that can identify you.

Please be advised not to visit other websites simultaneously with your online session, while you are still logged in and are viewing the information available on your account or you are performing online transactions with the help of CLARINTON Trading system. Do not forget to log off from your online session in CLARINTON Trading before you choose to move or access other websites, as well as prior to shutting down your computer.

Note that this web site may contain the links to other sites not related to CLARINTON Trading. In case you use non-CLARINTON Trading web sites, you'll be subjected to the privacy policies stipulates by those sites. CLARINTON Trading is not be responsible for the privacy policies practiced by non-CLARINTON Trading web sites.

Should you have any questions or require more information concerning this Privacy Policy or other practices of our site, please contact us on: [admin@clarintontrading.com](mailto:admin@clarintontrading.com)

By using this web site you accept our privacy policy. In case some terms are changed, all the changes will be reflected in this document. By using this web site after the changes in the terms took place, you as well agree to be bound by all of these changes.

## Anti Spam policy

Please be advised to read carefully our Anti-Spam Policy as we do not tolerate any kind of spam or similar activities.

Spam (unsolicited commercial e-mail) stands for an email message that is sent by you to someone who did not ask for it. There are different kinds of spamming. For example, posting inappropriate messages in different groups, message boards, chat, forums, etc.

CLARINTON Trading forbids sending unsolicited mass mailing of any kind. Our policy does not tolerate spam activities, and we will be forced to ban an account of any client who chooses to violate our anti-spam policy. Spam is not admitted in IRC channels or chat rooms, including Yahoo, AOL and other web chats, News Groups, as well as inappropriate use of Auction sites etc. Your account will be blocked that will result in loosing all your affiliates, and you will have to renounce from any unpaid money that were on your account.

For cases like that we strongly advise you to contact us using a special email address. If you think that someone uses CLARINTON Trading with the scope of spamming, please do contact us as soon as possible at the email: [admin@clarintontrading.com](mailto:admin@clarintontrading.com) \- and we will immediately apply the required measures.
